好  随便选一张牌
Okay, pick a card. Any card.
好了  记住
All right, now memorize it.
给大家看
Show it to everybody.
好了吗
Got it?
好  还给我
All right. Give it back to me.
红心5
Five of hearts.
这真是太神奇了
Real magic does exist.
乔伊  你是怎么做到的
Joey, how do you do it?
天机不可泄漏
I can't tell you that.
天花板上有人叫门了
Somebody's at the door on the ceiling.
我们楼上的芳邻吵得要命
That's our unbelievably loud upstairs neighbor.
他把地毯拆掉了  现在什么都能听到
He took up the carpets, and now you can hear everything.
你干嘛不上去要求他"轻声慢步"呢
Why don't you go up there ask him to just, "Step lightly, please?"
我试过五次了  但那家伙魅力无穷
I have, like five times. But the guy is so charming...
我上去大呼小叫  可最后还要跟他赔不是
I go up there to yell, then I end up apologizing to him.
太荒谬了
That is silly!
我上去叫他小声点
I'll go up there and I'll tell him to keep it down.
-好  请便  -祝你好运
- All right, be my guest. - Good luck.
好啦好啦
All right, all right...
如果你们真想知道  我就告诉你们
if you wanna know how I did it, I'll show you.
你把牌还给我的时候  趁你们不注意
When you handed me back the card, what you didn't see was...
我很快地看了一眼  肉眼是看不到的
I looked at it so fast, it was invisible to the naked eye.
我刚看了
I just did it.
又看了一眼
Just did it again.
我放慢动作好让你们看清楚  准备好没
Here, I'll slow it down so you guys can see it. Ready?
我懂了
Oh, I got it now!
谢谢
Thank you.
谁有一条六尺长的绳子
Anybody got a length of rope about 6 feet long,
末端有个绞索的
with a noose at the end?
-亲爱的  怎么了  -我刚看到珍妮斯了
- Honey, what's the matter? - I just saw Janice.
她在洛克菲勒中心和她丈夫溜冰
She was at Rockefeller Center, skating with her husband.
看起来幸福得很
She looked so happy.
我几乎不忍心拿那个小孩的椒盐卷饼打他们
I almost feel bad for whipping that kid's pretzel at them.
我记得跟凯萨琳分手后
I remember the first time I saw that girl
第一次跟她见面的情形
Katherine after we broke up.
她跟她朋友唐娜走在一块儿说笑
She was walking with her friend, Donna. Just laugh and talk.
老天  我难过死了
God, it killed me!
但你那天下午和她们两个上床了
Yes, but you ended up having sex with both of them that afternoon.
不好意思  我就是想说那件事
Sorry, I just any excuse to tell that story.
钱德勒  明天开派对  你会高兴起来的
Hey, Chandler, there's a party tomorrow. You'll feel better then.
我不会有事的
Oh, you know what. I'm gonna be okay.
你们不必为我开派对
You don't have to throw a party for me.
是乔伊的生日派对
It's Joey's birthday.
如果有人要开派对  那肯定非乔伊莫属
Oh, well. Then if anybody should have a party, it should be him.
我真不敢相信她还在楼上
I cannot believe she's still up there.
他完全讲砸了笑话的关键
Well, he totally screwed up the punch line.
应该是
You know, it's supposed to be
咖啡好了没有  亲爱的
How's that coffee coming, dear?
马上来  卡普兰先生
Yeah, right away, Mr. IKaplan.
我不应该喝咖啡  老是放屁
I'm not suppose to drink coffee. It makes me gassy.
我知道
I know.
你一定在想  "我这么聪明的女孩
I'll bet you're thinking, "What's an intelligent girl...
有志在服装界大展鸿图  怎么在这里泡咖啡"
who wants to be in fashion doing making coffee?"
被你猜中了
You got me.
别以为我没注意到你的潜力
Don't think I haven't noticed your potential.
我有一份和时装很有关系的工作要交给你
I've got a project for you that's a lot more related to fashion.
-听起来怎么样  -太棒了
- How does that sound? - That sounds great!
过来  亲爱的  来吧
Come on over here, sweetheart, come on.
太感谢了  卡普兰先生  太感谢了
Thank you so much. Mr. IKaplan. Thank you so much.
我要你马上把这些衣架分开
I need these hangers separated ASAP.
不客气
You're welcome.
老天  我痛恨我的工作  恨死了
Oh, God, I hate my job! I hate it. I hate my job, I hate it.
我知道亲爱的  我很遗憾
I know, honey. I'm sorry.
我想辞职  但我又觉得应该挺下去
I want to quit, but then I think I should stick it out.
然后我又想
Then I think:
为什么有人会做这种有损尊严的工作
"Why would such a person stay in such a demeaning job
难道就因为这份工作和兴趣有一点点关系吗
just because it's remotely related to the field they're interested in?
老天  我不知道  瑞秋
Gee, I don't know, Rach.
点菜吧  杨朵汤  詹姆斯豆
Order up! I got Yentl Soup, James Beans,
还有扯线玩偶豪迪杜迪
and a Howdy, hold the Doody.
亲爱的  对不起  我不是...
Honey, come on, I'm sorry. I didn't...
我不介意吃苦
I don't mind paying my dues, you know.
但搀扶得了关节炎的女裁缝上厕所
You know, it's just how much am I gonna learn about fashion...
我要怎样才能够
by walking Myra, the arthritic seamstress...
学会什么叫时装
to the bathroom?
你好
Hi.
我的痛苦很好笑吗
Is my misery amusing to you?
对不起  我只是...
I'm sorry, I was just....
这不好笑  这就是我的工作
It's not funny. This is actually my job.
相信我  我是过来人
Believe me, I've been there.
我以前曾在人体模特公司给模特头分类
I had to sort mannequin heads at that Mannequins Plus.
那么  我要继续跟我朋友聊天
Oh, well then. So I'm just gonna go back to talking to my friend here.
你可以继续享用你的汉堡
You can go back to enjoying your little hamburger.
还有一件事
Just one other thing.
什么事
Yes?
我在布明岱尔百货上班
I work at Bloomingdale's.
如果你有兴趣  我知道一个工作机会
I might know of a job possibly, if you're interested.
想吃我的腌黄瓜吗
Do you want my pickle?
大家好
Hey, guys.
-甘瑟  -你好
- Hey, Gunther. - Hi.
你要跟楼上吵闹的邻居约会吗
You're going on a date with the noisy guy upstairs?
他很迷人
Well, he's very charming.
他太迷人了
I know he's too charming!
但如果你们交往
But if you two start going out,
我就更难讨厌他了
then it's gonna make it much harder for me to hate him.
你只有尽力而为了
Well, you'll just going to have to try.
乔伊  果冻酒哪里去了
Joey? Where are the Jell-O shots?
不知道  钱德勒应该要派发的
I don't know. Chandler's supposed to be passing them...
钱德勒
Chandler!
哈罗
Hello-dee-lo!
看来你心情好多了
Well, somebody's feeling better.
-把舌头伸出来  -把衣服脱下来
- Stick out your tongue! - Take off your shirt!
我的天
Oh, my God!
你吃了多少  这是纯伏特加做的
How many of this did you have? These're pure vodka.
对  果冻  我妈以前做的就是这味道
Yeah, Jell-O. Just like Mom used to make.
我今天碰上了最不可思议的事
The most unbelievable thing happened to me today.
我在莫妮卡的餐厅吃午饭
So I'm having lunch at Monica's
有个家伙跟我说话
and this guy starts talking to me...
原来他是布明岱尔百货的采购助理
and it turns out he works for a buyer at Bloomingdale's.
他们的部门要招人
There happens to be an opening in his department!
我就把我的电话给了他
So I gave him my phone number...
他这个周末要打给我
and he's gonna call me this weekend
看看能不能帮我安排面试
to see if he can get me an interview!
-太好了  -就是
- Wow! - I know.
那家伙没有任何理由地帮你吗
What? So this guy's helping you for no apparent reason?
你根本不认识他
And he's a total stranger?
对  他叫"马克"什么的
Yeah. His name is "Mark" something.
看来"马克什么"的不怀好意
Sounds like "Mark Something" wants to have some sex!
什么
What?
不然他干嘛
I'm just saying, I mean, why else would he
莫名其妙地冒出来
swoop in and out of nowhere for no reason?
日行一善啊
To be nice?
乔伊  男人会不会没企图地对陌生女子行善
Hey, Joey, are men ever nice to strange women for no reason?
-不会  男人只想上床  -谢谢
- No, only for sex. - Thank you.
你有没有跟马克什么的提起我
So did you tell "Mark Something" about me?
我用不着提  因为我挂着
I didn't have to. Because I was wearing...
"我爱罗斯"的广告牌  而且一直摇铃铛
my "I Heart Ross" sandwich board and ringing my bell.
乔伊  生日快乐
Joey! Happy birthday!
你看到了多少个那个女生的重影
Okay, how many of that girls are you seeing?
你到底有多醉啊  她们是乔伊的姐妹
How hammered are you? These are Joey's sisters.
嗨  乔伊的姐妹
Hi, Joey's sisters!
都有些什么喝的
Hey, what're we drinking over here?
我喝的是伏特加和小红莓汁
Well, I have a vodka and cranberry juice.
真的
No kidding?
我干掉我丈夫之后
That's the exact same drink I made myself
就是调这种酒来喝
right after I shot my husband.
好吧  我不知道该怎么跟你说话
Well, I don't know how to talk to you.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
把我前任女友的快速拨号删除
Oh, I'm taking my ex-girlfriend of my speed dialer.
不  这是好事
No, it's a good thing.
我们要快速拨号干嘛  干嘛赶来赶去的
Why must we dial so speedily anyway? Why must we rush through life?
我们为什么不慢慢享受美好时光
Why can't we savor the precious moments?
你胸部好大
Those are some huge breasts you have!
我听说瑞秋今天遇到个叫马克的家伙
So I heard about this Mark guy that Rachel met today.
-很棒吧  -是啊
- Isn't it great? - Oh, yeah.
对  是很棒  听起来他是个好人
Yeah, pretty good. He sounds like a nice, good guy.
对  他可迷人了
Oh, he is. And he is so dreamy!
他走的时候  我引用了经典的胡言乱语
I mean, when he left, I actually used the phrase:
哈米娜  哈米娜  哈米娜
"Hummina, hummina, hummina."
太好了
That's excellent.
这么说他只是个大好人罢了
So he's "just a nice guy."
你真的认为这个叫马克的
Do you really think this Mark
是不求回报地帮你吗
doesn't want anything in exchange for helping you?
我想我得跟他洗鸳鸯浴
Well, I assume I'll have to take showers with him.
不过哪份工作不是这样
But you know that's true of any job.
你感觉怎么样
How you feeling?
我的公寓已经不存在了
Well, my apartment isn't there anymore...
因为全被我喝掉了
because I drank it.
你去哪里了  你拆开所有礼物之后就不见了
Where'd you get to? We lost you after you opened up all the presents.
我后来跑到贮藏室  而且不止我一个人
I ended up in the storage room, and not alone.
不要再叫了
No "woo-hooing." No "woo-hooing."
怎么了  发生了什么事
Why, what happened?
我上了乔伊的姐妹
I fooled around with Joey's sister.
这还不是最糟糕的
That's not the worst part.
那最糟糕的是什么
What is the worst part?
我不记得是哪个姐妹
I can't remember which sister.
你看到没有  别说男人有好人
You see what men do? Don't tell me men are nice.
这就是男人
This is men!
你疯了不成
Are you insane?
乔伊会杀了你  他真的会把你杀得死死的
I mean, Joey's gonna kill you. He's actually going to kill you dead.
你以为我没想到吗
Okay, You don't think I thought of that?
你怎么会不知道是哪一个
How can you not know which one?
简直无法置信
That's unbelievable.
-是吉娜吗  -哪个是吉娜
- Was it Gina? - Which one's Gina?
黑色蓬蓬头  戴着飞机耳环
The dark, big hair, with airplane earrings.
那不是吉娜  那是迪娜
No, that's not Gina, that's Dina.
看到没  你们也分不清谁是谁
You see? You can't tell which is which either!
我们可没有跟她们胡搞
We didn't fool around with any of them.
一定是维罗妮卡  那个穿红裙子的女孩
Veronica. Look, it's got to be Veronica. The girl in the red skirt.
我绝对有跟她舌吻
I definitely stuck my tongue down her throat!
那是我
That was me.
我喝醉后
Look, when I've been drinking,
有时会变得太热情
sometimes I tend to get overly friendly...
-对不起  -没关系
- and I'm sorry. - That's okay.
-不要紧  -没关系
- That's all right. - That's okay.
可以跟你私下谈谈吗
Can I talk to you for a second?
嘿  乔伊
Hey, Joey!
过来
Come on.
我们为什么不在这里谈
Why can't we talk in here...
这里有目击证人
with witnesses?
我刚跟我妹妹通完电话
I just got off the phone with my sister.
哪一个
Which one?
-玛丽·安琪拉  -玛丽·安琪拉
- Mary Angela. - Mary Angela.
她是哪一个
Now which one is she again?
不如问钱德勒吧
Why don't you ask Chandler.
因为他跟人家胡搞
'Cause he is the one who fooled around with her.
她告诉我  你说你为她而倾倒
She told me you said you could really fall for her.
这是实话吗
Now is that true?
还是你泡我妹妹只是为了忘记珍妮斯
Or are you just getting over Janice by groping my sister?
一定是第一个原因
It's gotta be the first one.
真的
Really?
那太好了
That's great!
你跟我妹妹坐在树上
You and my sister, sitting in a tree!
对  我在树上
Yep, I'm in a tree.
他来电话没有  马克来电话没有
Did he call? Did Mark call?
没有  我很遗憾  不过周末还没结束
No, honey I'm sorry. But the weekend's not over yet.
我的天  那是菲比吗
Oh, my God! Is that Phoebe?
看来他们的约会结束了
Guess they're back from their date.
音乐
Music!
真甜蜜
Very nice!
我的天
Oh, my God!
你好吗
So how are you?
我很好  我把书看完了
I am good. I finished my book.
是吗  讲什么的
Oh yeah? What's it about?
-我不记得了  你想散步吗  -想
- I don't remember. Do you want to take a walk? - Oh, yeah. I do.
亲爱的玛丽·安琪拉
"Dear Mary Angela:
嗨  你好吗
Hi, how's it going?
这是我所写过最难以启齿的一封信
This is the hardest letter I've ever had to write."
你是怎么搞的
What the hell's the matter with you?
你写信甩掉他妹妹
How do you think Joey's gonna react
乔伊会对你怎么样
when he finds out you blow off his sister with a letter?
这时候你就告诉他  我搬到法国去了
Well, that's the part where you tell him that I moved to France...
事实上  我人会在古巴
when actually I'll be in Cuba.
听我说  你得亲自去做这件事
Look, you've got to do this yourself okay? In person.
至少你知道她叫什么名字
At least, you know her name.
你只要到他家去找玛丽·安琪拉
You just go to the house and ask for Mary Angela. Okay?
不管她是哪一个  她到门口来的时候
When whichever one she is comes to the door...
请她去散个步  给她留点面子
you take her for a walk, you let her down easy.
万一是玛丽·安琪拉来开门
Okay. What if Mary Angela comes to the door
而我又开口找她呢
and I ask for Mary Angela?
你要去古巴哪里
Where in Cuba?
乔伊  你在这里干嘛
Joey, What are you doing here?
等我奶奶帮我洗衣服
Waiting for my grandma finish my laundry.
你呢
What about you?
我来见玛丽·安琪拉
I'm here to see Mary Angela.
你真是男子汉  来
You are so the man! Come on.
听我说
Now look, listen. Listen....
别乱讲话  因为奶奶还不知道你们的事
You got be cool, because my grandma doesn't know about you two yet.
最好不要惹她生气
And you don't want to tick her off.
她是第六个在墨索里尼的尸体上吐痰的人
She was, like, the sixth person to spit on Mussolini's hanging body.
玛丽·安琪拉在哪里
Where's Mary Angela?
她就在那里
She's right in there.
嘿  钱德勒
Hey, Chandler!
我不敢相信马克没有打电话来
I can't believe Mark didn't call.
现在是星期天晚上  他居然还没打电话来
It's Sunday night and he didn't call.
真叫人失望
Bummer.
看看你  一脸幸灾乐祸样
Yeah, right. Look at you. You're practically giddy.
我真的很遗憾  马克没有帮到你
I'm genuinely sorry the Mark thing didn't work out.
听我说  瑞秋  我也是一心为你好
Look, Rach, I want only good things for you.
等一下  为什么你不打电话给马克
Wait a minute. Why don't you just call Mark?
谁规定你得在这里痴痴地等
I mean who says you have to sit here and wait for him?
你得主动出击
You've got to make stuff happen!
对  但也不能太心急
Yeah, but you don't wanna seem too pushy.
不会的  他把家里电话给了她
It's not pushy. He gave her his home number.
他把家里电话给你  让你打电话到他家吗
He gave you his home number, as in, to his home?
你不介意我打电话吧
And you don't mind if I call,
既然你是一心为我好
because you only want good things for me.
没错  为你好  我是这么说的
That's right, good things. That is what I said.
你好  马克  我是瑞秋·格林
Hello, Mark? Hi, it's Rachel Green.
不  你千万别道歉
Oh, no. Don't you apologize.
好  我等着
Yeah, I'll hold.
他把电话号码留在办公室  本来要去拿的
He left my number at work. He was gonna get it.
不过他得帮他侄女做研究拓荒者的报告
But he was helping his niece with her report on the pioneers.
一听就知道是编的
That is so made up!
我的天  明天吗
Oh, my God! Tomorrow?
不  这太好了
That's No, it's perfect.
老天  太感谢你了
Oh, God! Thank you so much!
太好了  再见
Great. Bye.
我可以去面试了
I got the interview!
你看吧
There you go!
他还要跟我吃午饭  帮我准备
He even offered to meet me for lunch and prep me for it.
太好了
That is amazing!
如果我认识马克  我想是的
Well, if I know Mark, and I think I do...
他应该就是这种人
I'd expect nothing less.
我得想想明天要穿什么才好
I gotta figure out what I'm gonna wear.
高领衫加蓬蓬裤才是专业人士的穿着
High collar and baggy pants say, "I'm a pro!"
是啊
Yeah, right.
好了  回头见
Okay, I'll see you guys later.
没问题
You go get them!
我对你做过什么  我伤害过你吗
What did I do to you? Did I hurt you in some way?
什么
What?
你为什么不打电话给他
"Why don't you call him?"
真是太感谢你了  现在他要帮她准备
Thank you very much. Now he's gonna prep her...
帮她准备换言之就是
you know, prep her as in what you do
为开除现任男友做准备
before you surgically remove the boyfriend!
你疯了不成
Are you crazy?
有吗  我疯了吗  我失去理智了吗
Am I? Am I out of my mind? Am I losing my senses?
那个大帅哥要跟我的女朋友吃饭
This dreamy guy's taking my girlfriend out for a meal!
罗斯  你根本不是重点
Ross, this isn't even about you!
重点是瑞秋可以有好的前途
It's about Rachel, something wonderful happening for her.
就算你说得对  他对她不怀好意
Even if you're right, what if he wants to sleep with her...
这表示他就能得逞吗
does that mean he gets to?
-不会  可是...  -你不信任她吗
- No, but. - Wait, don't you trust her?
-当然不是  -那就别念叨了  成熟点
- Yeah. - Then get over yourself! Grow up!
你才别像个小孩子
You grow up.
这提拉米苏真好吃
This tiramisu is excellent.
是你做的吗  玛丽·安琪拉
Did you make it, Mary Angela?
不  是我做的
No, I did.
真好吃
Well, it's yummy.
那么
So....
玛丽·安琪拉  你喜欢吗
Mary Angela, do you like it?
当然  这是她最爱吃的
Of course. It's her favorite.
那么
So....
玛丽·安琪拉  你还喜欢什么
Mary Angela, what's your second favorite?
吃更多奶奶做的提拉米苏
More of Grandma's tiramisu.
拜托你
Oh, would you just please...
把食谱给我  因为太好吃了  简直是一流
give me your recipe, because this is great! It's topnotch!
食谱要跟我进棺材
That dies with me.
我也会
So will I.
到洗手间去
Excuse yourself and go to the bathroom.
我只是斜视  没什么特别意思
I was just squinting. It doesn't mean anything.
照做就是了
Just do it!
失陪一下  我得...
Will you excuse me, I have to....
终于  我还以为我们没机会独处了
Finally! I thought we'd never be alone.
听我说句话好吗
Can I just tell you something?
派对结束之后  我满脑子都在想你
I have not stopped thinking about you since the party.
听我说  我可能操之过急了
Look, I may have jumped the gun here.
我刚结束一段感情
I just got out of a relationship.
我还没办法
And I'm not really in a...
给任何人承诺
in a commitment kind of place.
那又怎样  我也一样
So? Me neither!
老天  玛丽·安琪拉说得对
God, Mary Angela was right.
你的嘴唇柔软极了
You do have the softest lips.
你不是玛丽·安琪拉
You're not Mary Angela?
不  我是玛丽·泰瑞丝
No! I'm Mary Therese!
这真是太糟糕了
This is so bad.
如果你不是玛丽·安琪拉  那谁是
If you're not Mary Angela, then who is?
我是
I am.
这真是太糟糕了
Oh, it's so bad.
乔伊
Joey.
不要叫乔伊  不要叫乔伊  乔伊
No, Joey! No, Joey! No, Joey! Joey!
怎么回事
What's going on?
就是你了  快去藏起来吧
You're it! Now run and hide!
没什么大不了的  钱德勒刚才亲我
It's no big deal. Chandler was just kissing me...
因为他以为我是玛丽·安琪拉
because he thought I was Mary Angela.
什么  你怎么会把她当成玛丽·安琪拉
What? How could you do that? How could you think she was Mary Angela?
我不确定哪一个是玛丽·安琪拉
I wasn't sure which one Mary Angela was.
对不起  我喝得醉醺醺
Look, I'm sorry. Okay? I was really drunk...
你们的样子都差不多
and you guys all look really similar.
-揍他  乔伊  -对  揍他
- I say punch him, Joey! - Yeah, punch him!
大家应该冷静下来
You know what. We should all calm...
因为你们的兄弟是不会揍我的
because, you know, your brother's not gonna punch me.
是吧
Are you?
我通常会这么做
That's usually what I'd do.
但我万万没想到有一天会揍你
But I just never thought you'd be on the receiving end of it.
你怎么能做这种事
How could you do this?
乔伊  如果你想揍我就动手吧  我罪有应得
Joey, if you wanna punch me, go ahead. I deserve it.
但我要你知道我在清醒时
But I just want you to know that
绝不会做伤害你和你家人的事
I'd never soberly hurt you or your family.
你是我最好的朋友
You're my best friend.
我再也不会做这种事了
And I'd never do anything like this, ever again.
那又怎么样
So what?
-我说揍他  -对  揍他
- I say punch him! - Yeah, punch him!
不  我不会揍钱德勒的
No, I'm not gonna punch Chandler.
-我来  -不  不行
- I'll do it. - No, you won't!
他知道他做了一件错事
Look, he knows he did a terrible thing,
我相信他是真心道歉了
and I believe him. He's sorry.
但你还要再跟一个人道歉
But you got one more apology to make.
你得跟玛丽·安琪拉道歉
All right, you gotta apologize to Mary Angela.
-当然  没问题  -好的
- Okay, absolutely. You got it. - All right.
-甜心  现在你可以揍他了  -什么
- Cookie, now you can punch him! - What?
你怎么来了
What are you doing here?
我顺路到这里来...
You know, this building's on my paper route, so....
面试怎么样
How did it go?
面试我的女人很难对付
Well, the woman I interviewed with was pretty tough...
但幸好有马克指点我
but you know thank God Mark coached me.
我一谈起秋季新装
Because, once I start talked about the Fall line,
她就满意得不得了  张口滔滔不绝了
she got all happy and wouldn't shut up.
-我真为你骄傲  -我也是
- I'm so proud of you. - Me too!
听我说  我...
Listen, I'm....
对不起  我这么神经又嫉妒...
I'm sorry I've been so crazy and jealous and....
这是因为我很喜欢你  所以...
It's just, I like you a lot, so....
我知道
I know.
-瑞秋  -你好  马克
- Rachel. - Hi, Mark.
我刚跟乔安娜谈过
I just talked to Joanna,
她很喜欢你  你被录取了
and she loves you. You got the job.
-真的  -是的
- I did? - Yes.
我的天
Oh, my God!
恭喜...
Congratulations....
菲比
So, Phoebe?
你的约会怎么样
How was your date?
你知道的
Oh, well, you know....
没错  我的确清楚
Yeah, I do know.
你偷听我们吗
You were eavesdropping?
偷听  菲比  天花板都快掉下来了
Eavesdropping? Pheebs, the ceiling tiles were falling down.
对不起
Oh, I'm sorry.
但我真的很喜欢他
But I really like this guy and
我想他也很喜欢我
I think he really happens to like me.
也许他只是
Maybe he's just...
跳弹簧单高跷跳得很爽
jumping on a pogo stick and he really likes it.
也许弹簧单高跷也被跳得很爽
Maybe the pogo stick likes it too.
好吧  到此为止  他不能这样对菲比
All right, that's it. He cannot do this to Phoebe!
我要狠狠揍这家伙一顿
This guy's gonna get the butt-kicking of a lifetime!
但他个子很高大吗
But is he a big guy?
我们一起去  走吧
We'll all go. Come on.
谢谢你们  谢谢
Thanks, you guys. Thank you!
别担心
Don't worry!
老天  希望他们痛扁他一顿
God! I hope they kick his ass!
亲爱的  我很遗憾
Honey, I'm sorry.
如果这可以给你一点安慰
If it's any consolation...
听起来他跟你在一起比较开心
he really did sound like he was having more fun with you.